{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"10.0.1","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":6900,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":11,"width":640,"height":480,"responsive":false,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"si1270","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4377","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4392","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_2","title":"Information Security Awareness Quiz Love Information Security ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_3","title":"Take our Security Quiz to test your knowledge.   Click on Begin to start. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_2","title":"Begin ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19016","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Begin ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19034","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Begin ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_106","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_106","title":"Brought to you by the Information Security Branch  Office of the Chief Information Officer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_234","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_234","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide4365","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","si4377","si4392","Text_Caption_2","Text_Caption_3","SmartShape_2","si19016","si19034","Text_Caption_106","Image_234"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4365"}}},{"id":"Image_235","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_235","roles":{}},{"id":"si12441","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_338","roles":{}},{"id":"si12349","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_327","title":"1.  Two factor authentication is offered up by security professionals as a “method and apparatus for positively identifying an individual.” Which of the following is an example of two factor authentication?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12382","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_332","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12386","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_333","title":"Having both a bankcard and a pin ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12382_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Having both a bankcard and a pin\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20585","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20589","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Having a password and a finger scan ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20585_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Having a password and a finger scan\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23460","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23464","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Having a key card and a password ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23460_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Having a key card and a password\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si31320","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31324","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31320_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si12435","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_337","roles":{}},{"id":"si12459","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_42","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_43","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19347","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19361","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19593","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19606","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19621","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19634","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19649","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19662","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19677","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19690","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_334","title":"Correct - Answer:  D  Two-factor authentication (also known as 2FA) is a type, or subset, of multi-factor authentication. It is a method of confirming users’ claimed identities by using a combination of two different factors: 1) something they know, 2) something they have, or 3) something they are. The two-factor authentication makes our information and data much more secure!   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12417","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_335","title":"Incorrect - Answer: D Two-factor authentication (also known as 2FA) is a type, or subset, of multi-factor authentication. It is a method of confirming users’ claimed identities by using a combination of two different factors: 1) something they know, 2) something they have, or 3) something they are. The two-factor authentication makes our information and data much more secure!   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12429","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_336","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12483","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_235","si12349","si12386","si20589","si23464","si31324","si12459","si12473","si19347","si19361","si19593","si19606","si19621","si19634","si19649","si19662","si19677","si19690","si12429"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12483"},"question":{"interactionId":"12329","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"1.  Two factor authentication is offered up by security professionals as a “method and apparatus for positively identifying an individual.” Which of the following is an example of two factor authentication?\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_242","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_242","roles":{}},{"id":"si29089","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_972","roles":{}},{"id":"si28986","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_953","title":"2.  Someone from your organization posts something unusual on the company social media website. What should you do?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28997","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_960","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29001","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_961","title":"Comment on the post ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28997_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_473","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Comment on the post\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si29008","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_962","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29012","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_963","title":"Share the post ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29008_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_474","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Share the post\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si29019","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_964","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29023","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_965","title":"Ignore the post ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29019_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"475","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ignore the post\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si29030","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_966","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29034","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_967","title":"Contact the individual and confirm they posted it ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29030_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"477","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Contact the individual and confirm they posted it\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si29083","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_971","roles":{}},{"id":"si29111","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_170","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide29278q1","for":"Slide29278q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29129","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_171","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide29278q1","for":"Slide29278q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29151","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_172","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide29278q1","for":"Slide29278q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29169","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_173","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide29278q1","for":"Slide29278q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29181","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide29278q1","for":"Slide29278q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29193","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide29278q1","for":"Slide29278q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29205","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide29278q1","for":"Slide29278q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29217","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide29278q1","for":"Slide29278q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29229","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide29278q1","for":"Slide29278q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29241","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide29278q1","for":"Slide29278q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29253","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide29278q1","for":"Slide29278q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29265","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide29278q1","for":"Slide29278q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29053","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_968","title":"Correct - Answer:  D  If someone from your organization posts something strange on company social media, you should contact them immediately to ensure that they have not been compromised. Here are a few social media tips to feel safe online and make you “love security”. Read and understand your organization’s social media policies. Don’t accept friend requests from people you don’t know. Ensure business information has been approved for release before it’s posted. Report suspicious events to your IT department. Make sure your privacy settings are reviewed regularly.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29065","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_969","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  D  If someone from your organization posts something strange on company social media, you should contact them immediately to ensure that they have not been compromised. Here are a few social media tips to feel safe online and make you “love security”. Read and understand your organization’s social media policies. Don’t accept friend requests from people you don’t know. Ensure business information has been approved for release before it’s posted. Report suspicious events to your IT department. Make sure your privacy settings are reviewed regularly.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29077","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_970","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide29278","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_242","si28986","si29001","si29012","si29023","si29034","si29111","si29129","si29151","si29169","si29181","si29193","si29205","si29217","si29229","si29241","si29253","si29265","si29077"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide29278"},"question":{"interactionId":"28966","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"2.  Someone from your organization posts something unusual on the company social media website. What should you do?\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_243","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_243","roles":{}},{"id":"si29428","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_985","roles":{}},{"id":"si29325","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_954","title":"3.  What is the main target of cyber criminals?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29336","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_973","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29340","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_974","title":"Company networks ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29336_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_478","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Company networks\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si29347","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_975","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29351","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_976","title":"Health care organizations ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29347_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_479","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Health care organizations\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si29358","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_977","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29362","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_978","title":"Senior citizens ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29358_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"480","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Senior citizens\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si29369","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_979","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29373","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_980","title":"Internet users ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29369_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"482","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Internet users\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si29422","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_984","roles":{}},{"id":"si29450","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_174","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide29617q2","for":"Slide29617q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29468","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_175","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide29617q2","for":"Slide29617q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29490","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_176","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide29617q2","for":"Slide29617q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29508","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_177","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide29617q2","for":"Slide29617q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29520","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide29617q2","for":"Slide29617q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29532","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide29617q2","for":"Slide29617q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29544","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide29617q2","for":"Slide29617q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29556","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide29617q2","for":"Slide29617q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29568","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide29617q2","for":"Slide29617q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29580","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide29617q2","for":"Slide29617q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29592","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide29617q2","for":"Slide29617q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29604","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide29617q2","for":"Slide29617q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29392","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_981","title":"Correct - Answer:  D  Over half of the world’s population uses the internet, and for this reason the ‘human attack surface’ is targeted ahead of machines.  If you find yourself targeted by cyber criminals, seek the help of a Cyber Security professional within your organization.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29404","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_982","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  D  Over half of the world’s population uses the internet, and for this reason the ‘human attack surface’ is targeted ahead of machines.  If you find yourself targeted by cyber criminals, seek the help of a Cyber Security professional within your organization.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29416","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_983","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide29617","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_243","si29325","si29340","si29351","si29362","si29373","si29450","si29468","si29490","si29508","si29520","si29532","si29544","si29556","si29568","si29580","si29592","si29604","si29416"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide29617"},"question":{"interactionId":"29305","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"3.  As summer vacation comes to an end, students and employees will be returning to school and work. Upon returning, many will need to either create new accounts or update passwords for existing accounts. What is the most important advice to always follow regarding passwords?\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_244","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_244","roles":{}},{"id":"si29767","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_998","roles":{}},{"id":"si29664","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_955","title":" 4.  When a web request is performed (like a user clicking on a link), approximately how many lead to malware?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29675","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_986","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29679","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_987","title":"1 in 4 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29675_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_483","roles":{"answer":{"title":"1 in 4\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si29686","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_988","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29690","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_989","title":"1 in 50 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29686_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_484","roles":{"answer":{"title":"1 in 50\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si29697","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_990","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29701","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_991","title":"1 in 27 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29697_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"485","roles":{"answer":{"title":"1 in 27\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si29708","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_992","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29712","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_993","title":"1 in 13 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29708_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"487","roles":{"answer":{"title":"1 in 13\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si29761","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_997","roles":{}},{"id":"si29789","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_178","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide29956q3","for":"Slide29956q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29807","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_179","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide29956q3","for":"Slide29956q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29829","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_180","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide29956q3","for":"Slide29956q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29847","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_181","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide29956q3","for":"Slide29956q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29859","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide29956q3","for":"Slide29956q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29871","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide29956q3","for":"Slide29956q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29883","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide29956q3","for":"Slide29956q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29895","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide29956q3","for":"Slide29956q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29907","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide29956q3","for":"Slide29956q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29919","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide29956q3","for":"Slide29956q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29931","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide29956q3","for":"Slide29956q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29943","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide29956q3","for":"Slide29956q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29731","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_994","title":"Correct - Answer:  D  Sadly, it is estimated that 1 in 13 web requests lead to some form of malware. Malware is challenging as it can act in a discrete fashion, making it difficult to detect whether a computer has been compromised. One reason to love security is that anti-virus software and firewalls can prevent intrusions.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29743","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_995","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  D  Sadly, it is estimated that 1 in 13 web requests lead to some form of malware. Malware is challenging as it can act in a discrete fashion, making it difficult to detect whether a computer has been compromised. One reason to love security is that anti-virus software and firewalls can prevent intrusions.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29755","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_996","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide29956","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_244","si29664","si29679","si29690","si29701","si29712","si29789","si29807","si29829","si29847","si29859","si29871","si29883","si29895","si29907","si29919","si29931","si29943","si29755"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide29956"},"question":{"interactionId":"29644","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":" 4.  When a web request is performed (like a user clicking on a link), approximately how many lead to malware?\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_245","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_245","roles":{}},{"id":"si30106","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1011","roles":{}},{"id":"si30003","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_956","title":"5.  What does the ‘s’ on “https://” at the beginning of a URL mean vs  “http://” (without the “s”)?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30014","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_999","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30018","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1000","title":"That the site has a fast connection (s for speedy) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30014_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_488","roles":{"answer":{"title":"That the site has a fast connection (s for speedy)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si30025","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1001","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30029","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1002","title":"That information entered into the site is encrypted ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30025_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_489","roles":{"answer":{"title":"That information entered into the site is encrypted\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si30036","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1003","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30040","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1004","title":"That the site has just been updated ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30036_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"490","roles":{"answer":{"title":"That the site has just been updated\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si30047","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1005","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30051","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1006","title":"That the site is only accessible by people in Canada ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30047_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"492","roles":{"answer":{"title":"That the site is only accessible by people in Canada\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si31335","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31339","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"None of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31335_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"None of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si30100","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1010","roles":{}},{"id":"si30128","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_182","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide30295q4","for":"Slide30295q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30146","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_183","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide30295q4","for":"Slide30295q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30168","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_184","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide30295q4","for":"Slide30295q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30186","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_185","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide30295q4","for":"Slide30295q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30198","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide30295q4","for":"Slide30295q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30210","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide30295q4","for":"Slide30295q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30222","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide30295q4","for":"Slide30295q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30234","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide30295q4","for":"Slide30295q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30246","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide30295q4","for":"Slide30295q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30258","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide30295q4","for":"Slide30295q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30270","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide30295q4","for":"Slide30295q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30282","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide30295q4","for":"Slide30295q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30070","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1007","title":"Correct - Answer:  B  Created in 1994 by security professionals working for Netscape Navigator web browser, HTTPS stands for Hyper Text Transfer Protocol Secure. HTTPS means that information entered into the site is encrypted, which makes it far more difficult for anyone other than the user and website owner to read the information.  Hooray for security innovations!  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30082","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1008","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  B  Created in 1994 by security professionals working for Netscape Navigator web browser, HTTPS stands for Hyper Text Transfer Protocol Secure. HTTPS means that information entered into the site is encrypted, which makes it far more difficult for anyone other than the user and website owner to read the information.  Hooray for security innovations!  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30094","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1009","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide30295","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_245","si30003","si30018","si30029","si30040","si30051","si31339","si30128","si30146","si30168","si30186","si30198","si30210","si30222","si30234","si30246","si30258","si30270","si30282","si30094"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide30295"},"question":{"interactionId":"29983","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"5.  What does the ‘s’ on “https://” at the beginning of a URL mean vs \r“http://” (without the “s”)?\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_246","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_246","roles":{}},{"id":"si30445","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1024","roles":{}},{"id":"si30342","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_957","title":"6.  Security Professionals are always looking to improve security through innovation. One such innovation predicted to greatly improve security is hardware authentication. What is hardware authentication?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30353","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1012","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30357","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1013","title":"User authentication that relies on a dedicated physical device (such as a token) held by an authorized user ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30353_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_493","roles":{"answer":{"title":"User authentication that relies on a dedicated physical device (such as a token) held by an authorized user\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si30364","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1014","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30368","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1015","title":"Placing passwords on computer hardware ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30364_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_494","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Placing passwords on computer hardware\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si30375","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1016","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30379","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1017","title":"Using facial scans and retinal scans to authenticate the user ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30375_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"475_495","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Using facial scans and retinal scans to authenticate the user\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si30386","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1018","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30390","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1019","title":"Ensuring that hardware does not come preloaded with anything malicious before using it in a device ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30386_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"477_496","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ensuring that hardware does not come preloaded with anything malicious before using it in a device\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si30439","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1023","roles":{}},{"id":"si30467","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_186","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide30634q5","for":"Slide30634q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30485","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_187","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide30634q5","for":"Slide30634q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30507","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_188","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide30634q5","for":"Slide30634q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30525","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_189","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide30634q5","for":"Slide30634q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30537","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide30634q5","for":"Slide30634q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30549","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide30634q5","for":"Slide30634q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30561","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide30634q5","for":"Slide30634q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30573","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide30634q5","for":"Slide30634q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30585","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide30634q5","for":"Slide30634q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30597","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide30634q5","for":"Slide30634q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30609","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide30634q5","for":"Slide30634q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30621","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide30634q5","for":"Slide30634q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30409","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1020","title":"Correct - Answer:  A  Hardware authentication is an approach to user authentication that relies on a dedicated physical device (like a mobile phone) held by an authorized user. The physical device will provide a unique and temporary code that the user will input along with their password to receive access to the computer.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30421","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1021","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  A  Hardware authentication is an approach to user authentication that relies on a dedicated physical device (like a mobile phone) held by an authorized user. The physical device will provide a unique and temporary code that the user will input along with their password to receive access to the computer.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30433","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1022","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide30634","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_246","si30342","si30357","si30368","si30379","si30390","si30467","si30485","si30507","si30525","si30537","si30549","si30561","si30573","si30585","si30597","si30609","si30621","si30433"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide30634"},"question":{"interactionId":"30322","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"6.  Security Professionals are always looking to improve security through innovation. One such innovation predicted to greatly improve security is hardware authentication. What is hardware authentication?\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_247","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_247","roles":{}},{"id":"si30784","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1037","roles":{}},{"id":"si30681","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_958","title":"7. If you need to use a public Wi-Fi network (such as in an airport or café), what cyber security innovation will help you remain safe?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30692","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1025","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30696","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1026","title":"A locking cable ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30692_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_497","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A locking cable\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si30703","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1027","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30707","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1028","title":"Pepper spray ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30703_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_498","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Pepper spray\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si30714","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1029","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30718","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1030","title":"VPN ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30714_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"480_499","roles":{"answer":{"title":"VPN\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si30725","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1031","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30729","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1032","title":"LOL ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30725_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"482_500","roles":{"answer":{"title":"LOL\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si30778","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1036","roles":{}},{"id":"si30806","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_190","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide30973q6","for":"Slide30973q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30824","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_191","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide30973q6","for":"Slide30973q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30846","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_192","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide30973q6","for":"Slide30973q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30864","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_193","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide30973q6","for":"Slide30973q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30876","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide30973q6","for":"Slide30973q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30888","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide30973q6","for":"Slide30973q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30900","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide30973q6","for":"Slide30973q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30912","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide30973q6","for":"Slide30973q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30924","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide30973q6","for":"Slide30973q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30936","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide30973q6","for":"Slide30973q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30948","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide30973q6","for":"Slide30973q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30960","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide30973q6","for":"Slide30973q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30748","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1033","title":"Correct - Answer:  C  A Virtual Private Network (VPN) allows users to create an encrypted connection between their devices and the internet, making it much harder for anyone other than the user to see their activity. Although this can’t guarantee your safety when using a public WIFI it will greatly improve your chance of staying secure Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30760","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1034","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  C  A Virtual Private Network (VPN) allows users to create an encrypted connection between their devices and the internet, making it much harder for anyone other than the user to see their activity. Although this can’t guarantee your safety when using a public WIFI it will greatly improve your chance of staying secure.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30772","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1035","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide30973","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_247","si30681","si30696","si30707","si30718","si30729","si30806","si30824","si30846","si30864","si30876","si30888","si30900","si30912","si30924","si30936","si30948","si30960","si30772"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide30973"},"question":{"interactionId":"30661","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"7. If you need to use a public Wi-Fi network (such as in an airport or café), what cyber security innovation will help you remain safe?\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_248","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_248","roles":{}},{"id":"si31123","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1050","roles":{}},{"id":"si31020","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_959","title":"8. Why should you love information security?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31031","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1038","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31035","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1039","title":"It can keep your information safe ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31031_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_501","roles":{"answer":{"title":"It can keep your information safe\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si31042","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1040","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31046","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1041","title":"It can teach you how to keep your personal belongings from getting stolen ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31042_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_502","roles":{"answer":{"title":"It can teach you how to keep your personal belongings from getting stolen\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si31053","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1042","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31057","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1043","title":"It has a very low level of unemployment ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31053_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"485_503","roles":{"answer":{"title":"It has a very low level of unemployment\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si31064","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1044","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31068","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1045","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31064_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"487_504","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si31117","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1049","roles":{}},{"id":"si31145","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_194","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide31312q7","for":"Slide31312q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31163","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_195","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide31312q7","for":"Slide31312q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31185","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_196","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide31312q7","for":"Slide31312q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31203","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_197","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide31312q7","for":"Slide31312q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31215","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide31312q7","for":"Slide31312q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31227","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide31312q7","for":"Slide31312q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31239","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide31312q7","for":"Slide31312q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31251","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide31312q7","for":"Slide31312q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31263","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide31312q7","for":"Slide31312q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31275","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide31312q7","for":"Slide31312q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31287","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide31312q7","for":"Slide31312q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31299","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide31312q7","for":"Slide31312q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31087","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1046","title":"Correct - Answer:  D  Information Security is a great thing to be passionate about. Along with keeping the information in our organizations safe, information security can also help to keep our family and friends’ information and physical devices protected. Beyond that, it is one of the fastest growing industries and will require many more professionals in the years to come. With all those reasons, what’s not to Love about Information Security?  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31099","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1047","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  D  Information Security is a great thing to be passionate about. Along with keeping the information in our organizations safe, information security can also help to keep our family and friends’ information and physical devices protected. Beyond that, it is one of the fastest growing industries and will require many more professionals in the years to come. With all those reasons, what’s not to Love about Information Security?  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31111","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1048","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide31312","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_248","si31020","si31035","si31046","si31057","si31068","si31145","si31163","si31185","si31203","si31215","si31227","si31239","si31251","si31263","si31275","si31287","si31299","si31111"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide31312"},"question":{"interactionId":"31000","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"8. Why should you love information security?\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_239","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_239","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_238","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_238","roles":{}},{"id":"si6059","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6083","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6091","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6055","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6079","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6087","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6103","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6107","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6121","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20489","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20502","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20517","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20530","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6038","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6038"}}},{"id":"si6231","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_240","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_240","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_241","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_241","roles":{}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19054","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19068","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_5","title":"Thank you for taking the quiz.  To exit the quiz, close the browser window. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":"  Stay Current With   Information Security   By Subscribing to the    Weekly Security News Digest ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6219","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","si6231","Image_240","Image_241","Button_4","si19054","si19068","Text_Caption_5","SmartShape_9"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":6000},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6219"}}},{"id":"Pool502","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":502,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"February2020Quiz","class":"project","title":"February2020Quiz","children":["Slide4365","Slide12483","Slide29278","Slide29617","Slide29956","Slide30295","Slide30634","Slide30973","Slide31312","Slide6038","Slide6219"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":458,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide12483q0","Slide29278q1","Slide29617q2","Slide29956q3","Slide30295q4","Slide30634q5","Slide30973q6","Slide31312q7"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":80,"passScore":64}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide4365","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide12483","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide29278","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide29617","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide29956","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide30295","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide30634","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide30973","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide31312","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide6038","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide6219","title":"Slide 11"}]}